bestcarinf.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Bestcarzin.com

_This document was last updated on May 09, 2014_

### GENERAL

**PURPOSE OF POLICY**

Bestcarzin.com (“us”, “we”, “the Site”) undertakes to respect the privacy rights of every visitors, users and others who use [Bestcarzin.com](http://www.bestcarzin.com/). Accordingly, we have developed the current privacy policy to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices. It explains how Bestcarzin.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from the visitors of the Site. The following outlines our privacy policy:

###  INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

**WHAT BASIC INFORMATION DOES THE COMPANY COLLECT?**

The Site can collect personal information from you in two situations. The first is if you should contact us via the “contact us” page. In this situation, you should provide us with your name and email address. The second is if you want to leave a comment to the posts during which you may be asked for a name and other information. 

**WHAT ADDITIONAL INFORMATION DOES COMPANY COLLECT?**

AUTOMATIC COLLECTION: When you visit to Bestcarzin.com, the servers will automatically track basic information about your interaction with our website as well as information that your web browser sends. Such log information includes, but is not limited to, the details of the browser, IP addresses, timestamps, referring pages, the address of the website you visited before you came to Bestcarzin.com, the data about your operation system and language. Any of such information cannot personally determine concrete visitors to this site. This kind of information is traced for routine management and maintenance.

COOKIES. Occasionally, we can use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to keep a small piece of data on your PC about your visit to the Site. Cookies support us to study which areas of the Site are advantageous and which areas need development through programs such as, but not limited to, Google Analytics. We may also use cookies from third party social sites and programs including, but not limited to, Twitter, Google Plus and Facebook. If you want, you can disable cookies through your browser or other software available online. However, if you disable cookies, your experience at the Site may be diminished as some features may not work as they were intended.

SPONSORS AND ADVERTISERS. We may decide to accept sponsorship and advertisements on the Site. If this happens, you need to take said sponsors and advertisers will have access to the impressions and click data on their marketing pieces. We will never reveal your personally identifiable information to them.

### USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION

**WHAT DOES COMPANY DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?**

ANONYMOUS INFORMATION. We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

USE OF COOKIES. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.

DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. We may disclose any information we have for you if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us, (2) protect and defend our rights or property or the users of the Site, or (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site.

### WEBSITE AREAS BEYOND COMPANY’S CONTROL

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

From time-to-time, the Site may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit those websites, it is important to understand our privacy practices and terms of use do not extend to those sites. It is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their practices.

### POLICY UPDATES AND CONTACT INFORMATION

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Bestcarzin.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time as we deem necessary or appropriate because of legal compliance requirements or changes in our business practices. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the top of this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of service](http://www.bestcarzin.com/terms_of_use). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS**

If you have questions or comments about Bestcarzin.com’s privacy policy, contact us by sending email to support@Bestcarzin.com. We read every message submitted and try to reply promptly to every one.

Thank you for choosing Bestcarzin.com!
